

MARCELA PETROLI

Front-end Web Developer

My Contact

Madrid, Spain

LinkedIn 🔗

GitHub 🔗

Portfolio 🔗

Technologies

REACT | | JAVASCRIPT | | JEST

NODE.JS | | EXPRESS | | SQLITE

HTML5 || CSS3 || SCSS || ZEPLIN

GIT || GITHUB || VSCODE || SLACK



Experience working within an Agile/SCRUM environment

Languages

Portuguese Native

English Bilingual proficiency Spanish Bilingual proficiency Italian Elementary proficiency

Education Background



TOEFL Preparation American Academy of English - San Francisco, USA

2016 - 2018



General English Program (C2) Embassy - San Francisco, USA 2015



Psychology Undergraduate Degree Unochapecó - Chapecó, Brazil 2009 - 2014

About Me

The love for constant learning, the challenge to keep up with the new and to belong to an amazing community such as the dev one, are the main reasons I decided to start my career as a web developer. I am my best version when working with people, sharing and learning together. Seeing the brighter side of things, learning with mistakes and being empathetic towards others, always.

Programming Experience

WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP, ADALAB - Madrid, Spain Sept - Dec 2022

- HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, Flexbox, Grid, responsive design.
- JavaScript (ES6) and APIs.
- SPA with React.
- Basics of Node.js, Express and SQLite.
- Git for version control.
- Remote work.
- Pair programming.
- Projects under Scrum framework and Agile methodology.
- Unit testing with Jest.

PROJECTS

STAR CARDS | |
Ø BREAKING BAD | |
Ø GUESS MY NUMBER

COURSES

- [In-Progress] The Complete JavaScript Course 2023: From Zero to Expert!, Udemy
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures, FreeCodeCamp,
- Scratch and Computational Thinking, KeepCoding, 2022
- Professional Course of Git and GitHub, Platzi, 2022

Professional Experience

English Teacher, Canterbury English - Madrid, Spain 2019 - 2022

Child Care, +60 families - San Francisco, USA 2015 - 2019

Administrative Assistant, Foods Parnoff - Chapecó, Brazil 2008 - 2015